

Swapnil Kalane GOVT Boys Hostel, BDD Chawl 118, Worli, Mumbai -400018 Maharashtra





+91.8421303403

Linkedin.com/in/swapnilkalane



About Me

Finance Professional

To secure the job in the Finance sector in your organization which could help me learn new skills and deliver my potential of financial analysis and strategic implementation of the new approach towards the development of the company.



Education

Masters, Management Studies

Allana Institute of Management Studies (1year)

AICTE & UGC Board

Mumbai, Maharashtra

Appearing Marks 60%

Division 1

Bachelor of Engineering in Computer science

Rajiv Gandhi College of Engineering & Technology

Nagpur University Board

Nagpur, Maharashtra

Graduated, July 2017

Marks 64%

Division 1

Diploma, In Engineering

Late Vasantdada Polytechnic

MSBTE Board

Nagpur, Maharashtra

Complete, Aug 2014

Marks 62%

Division 2

10+2

S.G. Boy's High School Paratwada

State Board

Amravati, Maharashtra

Graduated, July 2008

Marks 74%

Division 1

Professional Qualifications and Affiliations

- Successfully completed One Weekdays vocational training on at BSE Capital Management One Week Program (2019)
- Successfully completed One days vocational training on a on telecommunication systems at **Maharashtra Remote sensing Application Centre** (2015)

Career Highlights

Experienced Computer Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in Game Design, Python, java, java script, angular, Web Development, IoT, and Robotics. Microsoft Azure Architect, Amazon Web Services (AWS), Windows Server, Strong operations professional with a BE focused in Computer Science and Engineering from Rajiv Gandhi

College of Engineering and Research, Nagpur(University of Nagpur).

 Strong professional with Master of Management Studies focused in M.M.S in systems Engineering from University of Mumbai



- An **Analytical** approach to work.
- High Numeracy and sound technical skills.
- Mathematics
- Software Engineering
- Programming Languages
- Problem-solving skills and initiative.
- Negotiation skills and the ability to influence others.
- Patience
- Commercial and business awareness.

- Excellent communication and presentation skills.
- Strong attention to detail and an investigative nature.
- Learning
- Management

Work Experience

April 2018 – Current **Desktop Engineer**DSP Blackrock Pvt Ltd

Mumbai. Maharashtra

Desktop Support Engineers are IT professionals who fix issues with an organization's desktop computers and laptops, as well as handle concerns with servers and security issues affecting business networks. Desktop Support Engineers most often work as part of a helpdesk team, reporting to the Senior Systems Administrator or Engineer and sometimes supervise junior helpdesk employees. As computer issues can arise at any time, Desktop Support Engineers may be expected to work a variety of shifts, including nights and weekends. Although they are able to access other employees' computers virtually and mostly work from their office or desk, they may have to travel to individual work sites and server rooms, often being required to pick up and carry heavy equipment and parts.

- Knowledge of software engineering
- Background in IT
- Strong communication skills
- Problem-solving skills
- Ability to multitask
- Keep calm under pressure
- Programming experience
- Network security experience
- Training experience

Feb 2018 – March 2018 **Desktop Engineer & Server Support Engineer**Hinduja Hospital Pvt Ltd

Mumbai, Maharahstra

Desktop Support Engineers are IT professionals who fix issues with an organization's desktop computers and laptops, as well as handle concerns with servers and security issues affecting business networks. Desktop Support Engineers most often work as part of a helpdesk team, reporting to the Senior Systems Administrator or Engineer and sometimes supervise junior helpdesk employees

- Windows platforms
- Anti-virus
- Microsoft active directory
- Cloud platform

• Computer peripheral devices

Computer Proficiency

- Word 2010
- Excel 2010
- Power Point 2010
- Computer Language Java, Python etc.

? Languages

- Hindi
- English
- Marathi

Personal Interests

- Music
- Playing Games
- Meditation

- Reading
- Travel

O Personal Details

Father's Name: Mr. Suresh Kalane Marital Status: Single Birthday: March 03, 1993 Nationality: Indian

Gender: Male

Declaration

Swapnil Kalane

I, Swapnil Kalane, hereby declare that the information contained herein is true and correct to the best of my knowledge and belief.



Mumbai, Maharashtra